

Application Development Analyst seeking roles in Project Management, Software Development,Requirement gathering,Configuration Management,Quality Management,SAP Basis,SAP scripts,users Acceptance Testing ,SAP Implementation,Service Delivery



Current Designation: SAP ABAP Consultant Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 8 Month(s)

Current Company: Infosys Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: M.Tech [not specified]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried Key Skills: SAP ABAP,sap odata

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

- 3.5 Years of experience in SAP ABAP
- * Hands on experience of Adobe forms creation, reports creation ,enhancements, smartforms creation and hands on experience of solving incidents according to the requirement.
- * Hands on experience in RICEF objects along with OO ABAP

An associate sap ABAP Consultant with overall experience of 3 years in SAP, keen to work in a firm with a professional work driven environment where I can utilize and excel my knowledge, skills which would enable me to grow while fulfilling organizational goals and business requirements. I have worked extensively in SD, MM, FI Modules etc

Work Experience

Infosys as SAP ABAP Consultant Nov 2020 to Till Date

Accenture Solution as SAP ABAP Consultant Jan 2017 to Aug 2020

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (not specified) from Swami Ramananda Tirtha Institute of science and technology, Nalgonda in 2014

PG: M.Tech (not specified) from Osmania University college of engineering in 2016

IT Skills

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=e6a7c93dbb3cfd6095275c7d05cffd92095b0802431701455615155b0c0...

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
sap abap			
SQL,C			
SAP OO ABAP			

Projects

Project Title: JET tool Client: British Petroleum

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jul 2019 - Oct 2019
Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Skill Used: * SAP ABAP,* SAP OO ABAP

Project Details: Jet tool is an excel based tool for generating GL accounts , which required to design in sql and SAP ABAP , as an ABAP consultant involved in designing the required function module for the creation of this tool , which are to get the GL account details and validating them.

Project Title: BRITISH PETROLIUM Client: BRITISH PETROLIUM Nature of Employment: Full Time

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jan 2019 - Jul 2020
Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Skill Used: AP ERP (ECC 6.0) Project Details: Responsibilities:

Resolving tickets which would contain task as modifications, updates and troubleshooting existing ABAP objects.

Modification or added validations in existing BDC for different modules.

Modification in existing smart-form and layout creation.

Developed BDC program to change base line date in Accounting Document Details (FB02).

Designed layout for Sales Order and Enquiry form.

Participated in post-production testing which includes bug fixes and objects enhancements

Participated in Daily discussions with client regarding change request as onsite coordinator and its status & Handling Tickets and update the status to the Project Manager & Client on regular Intervals.

Recognize the critical elements of application problems, develop and evaluate data, determine solutions, and make logical recommendation.

Conducting Unit, Integration and release testing to validate functionality.

Project Title: Outokumpu Client: Outokumpu

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Apr 2017 - Dec 2018

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Skill Used: AP ERP (ECC 6.0)
Project Details: Responsibilities:

Developed back end objects like Function Modules, Reports, Custom TCodes, for various Apps Worked in various enhancements of standard Tcodes by using BADI, BAPI and Enhancement spots.

Problem resolving related to data loading and query performance.

Created order acknowledge form SD, invoice form FI.

Worked on Idoc changes related to MM

Modified global invoice for local needs of 5 countries.

Participated in preparation, distribution and collaboration of client specific quality documentation on developments on ECC landscapes along with regular monitoring on reflecting the modifications or enhancements done in landscape to SolMan (Solution Manager) Tool.

Worked extensively on RICEF while gaining knowledge of business processes minding user satisfaction.

Done translation work for reports, forms, SAP scripts, text modules, messages, and SO10 texts.

Directly interacted with Users for their requirement.

Involved in requirement gathering for the report.

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time